I mean a good health insurance plan
supports you and your family when you
sleep on one bed and it is very important for you to have a
good health insurance plan, for this
we made a video in
which we discussed the top three plans of India
and also ranked them
and saw how number one is Gypsy,
number two is Start and number 3 is Release, the
video link of that will be in the description and i button,
that video is almost going to make
5000 because of your love and you
keep showing such remedies and love, right now
in that video you have many questions, you have to go through a
lot of details, that is
why I have decided that
on this channel, first of all we will tell you about HDFC Ergo
which is India's best plan, our code and
for that you should know the details, know its features
and it is very important to know one thing and you have many
doubts which I need to solve,
in this video we will cover everything related to the best health insurance plan of MSD
which was earlier also called Apollo,
if
you want then we will also cover Star
and Religare  We will also make a video on this. We
came on this. First and most important is for
you to know what are the features of acid serials,
why we kept it number one
in our ranking and also what are such
things, some such features, some such details which
you should not miss. My name is Anant
Laddu, just because of this, Shed also and welcome all of you
to your channel whose name is
Nivesh Soch for tomorrow. Let's start today
's discussion. Before that, please subscribe to this channel
and click on the bell icon right now,
otherwise it should not happen that some important
video gets mixed with you. Let's start today's
discussion on that. First of all, let's
understand HDFC Ergo.
Earlier it was also known as Apollo.
It last launched a policy of more than Rs. 10 lakh
in India, which is the highest
in the industry. Its death claim
rate is Rs. 10 lakh. You should know the scene in which
these cut trees are cut. What happens to how much
premium have they collected against that,
how much have they refused to
return to the trees, that is,
in how many classes have they returned it to them. Their
rate is 60%.  The ratio of any health
insurance company should be
between 50% to 85%.
60% of them, which is very
good, is a good thing here and we will have to
note this. Next, it is important to know that
first you go to schools and as this Apollo
brand is associated with Africa, then it has become an even bigger
network of hospitals. Its almost a
thousand plus hospitals in today's Dead Sea
Argograph Plant provide you cashless treatment.
Next, you need to know
how much you can understand. The minimum is
relaxed and the maximum is
text impression. If we talk about treatment, then
such a time answer is more than 35,000
hospitalizations, then all your
expenses, whether it is related to ICU, room
rent, medicine
related, diagnosis related,
options or fans of anything, are covered in
mode on the policy. There is no room rent for you in this policy,
whatever you have to pay for this room will be applicable.
Pre-hospital expenses such as
Bigg Boss gets well or you get medical
consultation or medicine and any such
expenditure is
available to you for 60 days after free hospitalization.
Post hospitalization,
this
expenditure is available to you from the 1st day after hospitalization. The
point of no claim bonus is
very important for you, listen to it carefully, it is the
most important point.
In every year, if
your no claim bonus will not be cleared till now, it will
increase your total semester value by 50%, meaning if your
policy does not come for one year, then
instead of 5 lakhs, it
means seven and a half lakhs, if it does not come for 2 years, then
your policy will go to 10 lakhs and
so your initial semester bonus is of 5 lakhs but after paying the no
claim bonus, it will give you 10 lakhs,
the maximum can only be doubled, it cannot be doubled,
meaning if any friend did
not come for his first 2 years, then whatever
you had understood in the third year, it will double
and keep one thing in mind, whenever you plan
anything, then  It will be
reduced directly, you will have to understand that, the
next important thing is the restore
benefit, what kind of point is this, due to which we had
kept HDFC Ergo at number one,
Star at number two or Rally Ghar at number
three, the most main benefit that
HDFC Ergo has today is
its most flexible resort benefit
and the best is what is the second benefit,
as soon as any of your claims comes, you are
thwarted hundred percent, I mean,
understand that your basic is always 5 lakhs,
your no claim bonus increases to 10 lakhs
and you have the Maya of ₹4000 pure
silk - Ramesh Sharma of Chawla Chhaila,
Shweta ji, no six lakhs, this 5
lakhs will be increased and 11 lakhs will be given to you, I
mean, understand as much as you have hinted, as soon as
any claim comes, the Muslim will be
thwarted and restored
and this is the best in Gypsy and the most
important point is if you are having any acidity for
which you need to take a second
For me, even in the resort, that game
alarm turns you off, which is the
most lovely point, that is why
I kept this Gypsy at number one. Keeping this point
in mind, the next important
point is Deccan Chargers and Deccan
process. Whenever you
go to the hospital and get admitted for
less than 24 hours, then it is in Deccan.
All these charges are
included. You will see in your policy document, there is a
print
documentation from the country, there is a print department
accept section in which you will get
all the details related to this. If you
still have any doubt related to this, we
will discuss computers in this video, even after that, if you have
any doubt in your mind, whether I have
combined it in the description and even the first one, in which there is
a number of the central office of ad serials
or direction, your number, any doubt, then
you should ask them, as if it will be according to
tomorrow or mine, then you will get 100% help
and you will get better service and you will get
a neutral advance and whatever you
Advice will be given as per the details as possible, we will
help you in everything, the number of the central office
is there, don't worry you can ask anything
without any confession, without any
diet, without any doubt that I am
not providing any wrong information, all the
notes will go to your home. Next important thing is
home treatment. Now we move on to the
next home treatment. Will
we provide treatment to the patients? The treatment plant will definitely be available
but there will be some terms and conditions.
What will be the conditions before this? How
can it be possible that the patient is
not possible to shift him to the hospital or he should be
shifted to the hospital if it is
not available there. An important
point for this is that if the treatment is for more than three days, it means there should be
medical treatment and that too under the
guidance of a medical practitioner. It should not happen that
such treatment is given at home. This is important.
Free
questions are provided but post
hospitalization is not accurate at the time of home treatment.
You need to know that there is an
ambulance charge. Next point in
which you will get ₹2000 for the operation. There is
also a special feature of air ambulance
but this  It is only available in your policy
whose total sum assured is above 10 lakhs, maximum up to
2.5 lakhs, for 10 lakhs you get
recording, this you get air
ambulance but it is necessary to have minimum 10 lakhs, will
you get an organ donor
or if someone donates an organ to you, then
all his expenses, the one who is donating will
also get improved
but the amount will be reduced as per your Owaisi policy,
health checkup means
whenever you get a higher mode of health checkup done,
you will get free, this point is
considered as a turn, means in the five lucky policy, in this every two years,
you
can get a refund once after every two years in the
name of health checkup in the family,
if you have taken a family floater then ₹3 and if you have taken it for
individual then ₹10
and in the policy of 10 lakhs, you get every
year which is such in which airplane cannot be used,
₹5000 in case of family and Dr.
₹2000 can be taken in the name of health check-up in submarine cases.
You people
forget to take rest in many cases.
Documentation is required. Whenever
you take a health policy under SD Senior Group,
then you always have to take this insurance.
If any of your insurance is not mentioned in the policy, which will
increase for free. Similarly, the amount
of insurance will also change. You will have to
see at your basic level what
is your 1.5 balance program from the net. If you
remain active and download their mobile app,
you would get some discount
on renewal. You should
follow all the things and whatever you give in that too. The
next important point is the maximum age,
maximum at 4 new issues of the policy,
sixty-five years. This will have to be kept in mind.
But there will be a rain, after that it can
continue till the policy is in place.
How many people can be included in a family floater? After that,
maximum six people can be included.
But if properly prepared, you can
never buy a family floater.  In a family floater, the
premium is decided in that family
floater which is linked to the highest premium.
Therefore, never include
your elder parents who have more than one child in your family policy.
Keep your wife and children and take your princely state
policy, otherwise your
premium will increase unnecessarily because
when these are family members, it will be for five people or
four people for free and it will be
decided on the basis of who has the highest
premium. If you have
parents who have more than one child, then your
free family floater premium will
increase a lot. So, I suggest you to
give a successful policy to your elderly parents. Do not enroll them in your policy. The
next important point is if you take
2 years premium together, then does it
reduce anything? Yes friends, if
you take 2 years premium together, then
you get a discount of 7.5 lakh rupees. I mean, I
suggest that if you keep the payment for the second term, you can do it if your
financial condition is good. If you are getting 2
more years
discount, then why?
Explosions should not be taken, you must make a list of exclusions
once, there are many
diseases, not just a few, there are some
things like STD or
HIV or normal OPD or
maternity charges, these are covered by many policies, so
always do the exclusions,
please West Indies, this question is a 3
year thing, it is asked many times
and you do not get any reduction in pre-existing diseases for the first three
years, you
need to know, the next important point comes whether
this story is based, Edison had one of the
biggest, Apollo was also very good, as
you have got along with Oil and BSC, so
its goodness or its network has increased further
and today for investors or
whoever wants to take a policy, my contact
number one is Apollo, number two is Tes and number
three, we will make a video of number two and number three,
if you want, if you want a similar detailed video, then
we will make that too, its
last point is the premium,
almost we keep everyone's premium, but Africa
This is very complicated, the
premium will be different based on
how many children you have in the family floater, if the
children are rudimentary then I will
take it on the basis of the maximum amount, I will get you the maximum amount on my first exam, then it will be a
better idea, for example, I want to take
₹5 PM, a person who is 38
years old, there are two children in his family
and he and his wife, husband, wife and two
children, the maximum age of which is
30 years for the husband, the family floater should be
₹500, its premium if it is
in Delhi-NCR then it will be almost ₹1628,
this is the example, now you
can think how PM is a big loss,
if you need any more information,
you will get the information within 15 minutes, there is a
helpline number in the description, you can connect on it, you
can connect to the helpline number of 1.5-1.5 C Alok and you will get direct
information within 2 minutes, and if you
take it from here then you get many discounts and many other
things which you get  If you are
going then do the mixture if you
still have some doubts, whenever you take a policy,
clear all your doubts and
read everything beforehand, then any article, any
doctor, I have mentioned in the description and even faster, in
which I have
given the number, you can connect,
do you want me to make a video of Star and Rally Ghar
Ka Paisa, then tell me by commenting,
if you get a lot of requests to do this,
I have received mails on almost quality that you should make a
video of HDFC audit, now in these four rallies
also, if you want, I will make that, tell me by commenting
that you want us to
make all four-layer also, otherwise my coding
tips are one of the best for you,
I will edit it today, if you want, you
can take it from here, we will meet in the next video, till then
you can check out Investigate and I miss you very soon,
our serial on Options is
going on very interestingly, I am getting a lot of love from you,
if you have not
seen the dish from it, then watch the option thing cooked on this channel
and subscribe to this channel
without any hassle and if you want to connect with us on any social media,
Description  I have given the link,
you can add me on Telegram, more than that, I am sure I will be
added, we will
meet in the next one, till then you are investing,
if you want our mutual fund or any
financial planning related services, there
is a separate helpline number for that,
you can connect with it.